Khawer Ali

Full Stack Developer

I have 5 years of experience as a PHP developer and have worked in the field since I graduated with my bachelor's degree. As a developer, I have worked on both small and large projects. I am able to work independently as well as collaboratively with others on teams.





khawerali29@gmail.com

+923472530441



Pakistan DHA, Karachi, Pakistan



in linkedin.com/in/khawer95

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer Salsoft Technologies

11/2021 - Present

Karachi

Laravel, Vue Js and Nuxt Js Projects

- Using tech stack of Laravel MVC Framework, PHP, MySQL, Git, Vue Js, Nuxt Js and MongoDb,
- Managed a team of 5 people working on different Projects,
- Achieved 100% on-time project delivery to meet the regulatory milestone,
- Working experience with JIRA and Bitbucket (as well as the Git code repository, including code-reviewing tools),
- Experience working with Agile and Scrum teams.

Laravel Developer MT Pixels (Pvt) Ltd

01/2021 - 09/2021

Karachi

Laravel Projects

- Work as part of a creative and technically excellent team.
- Experience developing well-organized, maintainable, objectoriented, unit-tested code in PHP.
- Experience developing highly scalable and composable RESTful APIs.
- Experience developing REST applications on modern MVC PHP frameworks such as Laravel.
- Experience with MySQL (relational concepts, SQL, ER diagrams).

Php Developer

The Next Rex (Pvt) Ltd

01/2019 - 12/2020 Karachi

Laravel and Codelgniter Projects

- Experience with MySQL (relational concepts, SQL, ER diagrams).
- Experience with REST APIs, with a basic understanding of object-oriented programming (OOP) design patterns.
- Designing, coding, and testing customizations, as well as working with different team members to deliver complex changes.

Web Developer

IMS Engineering (Pvt) Ltd

01/2018 - 12/2018

Karachi

Achievements/Tasks

- Wordpress Website
- Admin Panel Support
- Html Bootstrap Websites

SKILLS



PROJECTS

Day4Dubai Web and App (Dubai Government Project)

Video Streaming Web App & Mobile APIs with Live Streaming (Like YouTube).

ERP for Sharmeen Group of Companies

Multi Users Donation Web App

Multivendor Ecommerce Web and App (Daraz Replica).

Multi Users Donation Web and App

EDUCATION

MASTERS IN PROJECT MANAGEMENT

Szabist University

09/2022 - Present

Karachi

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

Igra University

2014 - 2019

Karachi

CONFERENCES & COURSES

International Leadership Conference - 16 Institute Of Business Administration

Corporate Connect (04/2016)

Igra University

Hardware & Network Solutions (02/2011 - 04/2011) Skill Development Council

Certification